Guide to the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Information Files, 1879-present CTC.Infofiles.Pgh
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Information Files
1879-2022
1974-1998
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Curtis, Harriet R.
Curtis, Ford E.
CTC.Infofiles.Pgh
12 Linear Feet (9 boxes)
The Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Information Files contain programs, news clippings, press releases and other materials about Pittsburgh performing arts groups, individuals, and venues. There is at least one folder in the Information File for each of the headings listed below.
Accruals
New materials are added to the collection by the staff of the Curtis Theatre Collection. Donations are occasionally added to the collection. These donations come from the producing groups themselves or members of the public. If you are interested in donating materials to the collection, please contact the Archives & Special Collections department staff.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Related Material
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Theatre Programs, 1840-, CTC.1966.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Photographs, 1907-present, CTC.1966.03, Curtis Theatre Collection,Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains newspaper clippings, programs, and other ephemera relating to performing arts companies in the Pittsburgh area. It also contains files with materials relating to individuals from the Pittsburgh area. The files are arranged alphabetically. Please note that while some of the dates listed for the folders go back to the nineteenth century, most of the older clippings are preservation photocopies and the originals have been discarded. Materials are sometimes transferred from this collection to the Curtis Collection of Pittsburgh Theatre Programs.
Theater programs; Clippings (Information artifacts); Theater -- Production and direction; Actors -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Motion picture industry -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Dinner theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh
- A
  - AAFC - SEE Actors and Artists of Fayette County
  - ACBA Players - SEE Allegheny County Bar Association Players
  - APA Theatre Company - SEE American Performing Arts Theatre Company
  - A.R.T. - SEE A Renaissance Theatre
  - A Renaissance Theatre, 1986
  - Aberlin, Betty, 1979-1981
  - Abraham, F. Murray, 1990
  - Absolute Pitts, 2001-2002
  - Academy Players, 1959-1970
  - Ackerman, Robert Allen, 1990
  - Acorn Theatre Company, 1995-1998
  - Act One Theatre Company, 1989-1993
  - Acting Company, 1992-1998
  - Actors-Miscellaneous - SEE Talent
  - Actors and Artists of Fayette County, 1994
  - Actors and Artists of Fayette County, 1979-1996
  - Adkins, Paul Spencer, 1990
  - Adler, Joe, 1989
  - African American Council of the Arts, 2004-2006
  - African American Renaissance Theatre, 1985
  - AIDS and the Performing Arts, 1989-1991
  - Al Smith Players - SEE East End Theatre
  - Albee, Edward, 1990
  - Aldine Theatre, 1920-1926
  - Alhambra Theatre, 1918
  - Allegheny Centennial - SEE Drama Festival of Allegheny Centennial
  - Allegheny College, 2007-2009
  - Allegheny Community Theatre, 1975-1977
  - Allegheny County Bar Association Players, 1982-1998
  - Allegheny County Sesquicentennial, 1938
  - Allegheny County Medical Society, 1985
  - Allegheny Highland Regional Theatre, 1988-1997
  - Allegheny Theatre Guild, 1940
  - Allegheny Valley Concert Association, 1973-1976
  - Allen, Marty, 1974-1985
  - Allen, Ralph, 1990-2004
  - Alliance of Pittsburgh, 1980-1981
  - Allison, Lisa, 1990
  - Alper, Robert, Rabbi, 1989
  - Alvin Theatre, 1900-1998
  - Ambrosio, Nora, 1991
  - American Conservatory Theatre, 1960-1988
  - American Dance Ensemble, 1978-1979
  - American Dance Guild - Pittsburgh Chapter, 1972
  - American Experimental Theatre Company, 1984-1985
  - American Film Theater, 1974-1975
  - American Performing Arts Theatre Company, 1980-1984
  - Amphitheatre, 1989
  - Amusement Tax, 1988-1995
  - Anderson, George, 1982-1985
  - Andrews, Julie, 1989
  - Andy Warhol Museum, 1996-current
  - Animal X, 1990
  - Annaud, Jean-Jacques, 1989
  - Annegarn, Steve, 1989-1990
  - Annie II, 1989-1990
  - APA Theatre Company, 1985-1988
  - Appalachian Spring (Film), 1959
  - Applewhite, Charles, 1990
  - Apt, Joan, 1991
  - Arabica Coffee Houses, 1994
  - Arcade Theatre, 1979-1984
  - Arcadia Theatre, 1923
  - Arena Theatre, 1951
  - Ariodante
  - Art Cinema, 1935-1989
  - Artery, The, 1990-1994
  - Arthur, Lee, 1989
  - Artichoke Theater
  - Artists Raising the Consciousness of Humanity Productions, 1994
  - Arts tax, 2009
  - Arts Therapy, 1990
  - Asbury Musical Theatre Guild, 1982
  - Aspinwall Drama Workshop, 1976
  - Assumption Theatre Guild, 1993
  - Atelier Theatre
  - Atkins, Tom, 1975-1990
  - Attack Theatre, 2002-2008
  - Auberjonois, Rene, 1979-1990
  - Audience shots
  - Audience surveys, 1975
  - August Wilson Center, 2013-current
    Scope and Content Notes
    These newspaper articles detail the August Wilson Center's 2014 financial crisis.
  - August Wilson House, 2003-current
  - August Wilson New Voices competition, 2024
  - August Wilson Society, 2018
  - Avenue Cinema, 1931
  - Axiom Theatre, 1994-1995
- B
  - BB Productions, 1983-1985
  - Bach Choir of Pittsburgh, 1986-1991
  - Backroom Theatre - SEE Fountain Room Restaurant. Backroom Theatre
  - Badlands Theatre Company, 1993
  - Bail, Chuck, 1976
  - Balada, Leonardo, 1989-1990
  - Baldwin Players Community Theatre, 1974-2002
  - Bales, William
  - Ball, William, 1961-1991
  - Bansavage, Lisa, 1983-1990
  - Bare Bones Players, 1980
  - Baron, Christy, 1989-1990
  - Barth School of Dance, 1926-1929
  - Baskin/Kravitz, 1975-1978
  - La Bastille Dinner Theatre
  - Bavier, Frances, 1989
  - Beckett, Samuel, 1989-1990
  - Beck's Patio Theatre, 1964-1967
  - Beckwith, Shiras Patterson, 1990
  - Bedford, Brian, 1989-1990
  - Bedford County Players
  - Belmar Theatre
  - Ben Gross Restaurant, 1980-1983
  - Bennett, Henry M., 1902-1976
  - Benson, George, 1989
  - Bensen, Michele, 1990
  - Bernhardt, Sarah, 1880-1881
  - Beruh, Joseph, 1976
  - Bethany College
  - Betty Caplan Productions - SEE Caplan, Betty
  - Beverly Hills Playhouse, 1963-1983
  - Bicentennial - SEE Pittsburgh Bicentennial
  - Bicsey, Jon
  - Big Gee Marionette Cereal Players, 1986
  - Biggar, Laura, 1902-2003
  - Bijou Theatre
  - Bimbo's
  - Binotto, Paul, 1986
  - Birmingham Lofts, 1991
  - Black Horizons Theatre, 1969-1972
  - Black Theatre Festival, 1991
  - Blairsville Drama Guild, 1975
  - Blarney Stone Restaurant, 1979-1995
  - Bloomfield Civic Playhouse, 1948
  - BLT Productions - SEE ALSO Hoover, Ted, 1985
  - Blue Angel Restaurant - SEE Performing Arts Theatre
  - Blue Collar Players, 1991
  - Bob Warren Productions - SEE Warren, Bob
  - Booking agents - SEE Marice, Sid
  - Boseman, Chadwick
  - Bosson, Barbara, 1991
  - Boudreau, Robert, 1989-1990
  - Bounce the Clown & Mademoiselle Ooo La La's Vaudeville Circus, 1987
  - Bouquett, Tamara Tunie, 1990
  - Bourne, Mel
  - Bradford Woods Couples Club, 1974
  - Brannigan Family, 1976
  - Brecht, Bertolt Productions, 1989
  - Bricolage Production Company, 2002-current
  - Brier Hill Playhouse
  - Brightman, Sarah, 1990
  - Brighton Theatre, 1980
  - Brion, Keith, 1989
  - Broadway Players Stock Company, 1923-1924
  - Brockett, Don, 1966-1998
  - Brodhead Community Players, 1981-1983
  - Brooke Hills Playhouse, 1983
  - Brourman, Michele, 1976
  - Brown, Jason, 1984-1986
  - Brown, Kirk
  - Browne, Roscoe Lee, 1989-1990
  - Brownsville Summer Playhouse, 1970
  - Buba, Tony, 1989-1994
  - Bucket Dance Theatre, 1987
  - Burlesque, 1977-2006
  - Business Volunteer for the Arts, 1990-1991
  - Butler County Community College, 1982
  - Butler Little Theatre, 1975-2005
  - Byham Theatre
- C
  - CHP Players - SEE The Pittsburgh Academy of Medicine
  - Cabaret Theatre, 1979-1984
  - Cafe la Place, 1993
  - Cafe Stephen B's
  - Caldra Players, 1937-1939
  - California State College, 1977-1981
  - California University of Pennsylvania, 1985-1993
  - Calliope House, 1986-1990
  - Calvert, Robert, 1978
  - Campaneria, Miguel, 1990
  - Campbell, Bartley, 1879-1949
  - Caniparoli, Val, 1989
  - Cap in Hand Productions, 1992
  - Capecci, Michael, 1990
  - Capitol Theatre, 1923
  - Caplan, Betty, 1973-1987
  - Capobianco, Tito, 1983-1989
  - Caravan School of Theatre Arts (including Caravan Players, Caravan Theatre), 1943-1948
  - Carlow College (including Mount Mercy College), 1957-2002
  - Carlow College, 1973-2008
  - Carnegie Lecture Hall, 1946-1995
  - Carosella, John
  - Carousel Theatre, 1991
  - Carra, Larry, 1976-1979
  - Carreras, Jose, 1990
  - Carriage House Players, 1976-2007
  - Carrick Players, 1940
  - Cascio, Anna Theresa, 1989
  - Casey, Rosemary, 1950-1976
  - Casino Theater, 1896-2009
  - Cast Players, 1938
  - Cather, Willa, 2014
  - Celebrations - SEE Festivals, Celebrations, Pageants, etc.
  - Censorship, 1932-1991
  - Center for American Music, 1996-1998
  - Center for Theatre Arts, 1984-1988
  - Center Stage Players (Jewish Community Center), 1975
  - Center Stage Players - SEE Washington and Jefferson College
  - Chancery Lane Players, 1974-1975
  - Characters East, 1974-1982
  - Charisse, Cyd, 1989
  - Charity Randall Theatre, 2003
  - Chesterfield's Restaurant - SEE Theatre Limited
  - Children's Civic Theatre Society, 1949-1953
  - Children's Hospital Players - The Pittsburgh Academy of Medicine
  - Children's Hospital Variety Club, 1969-1985
  - Children's Museum, 1986
  - Children's Center for Theatre Arts, 1983
  - Children's Theatre Workshop, 1981
  - Christopher's, 1982
  - Cinemette Corporation, 1983
  - Circus, 1975-1990
  - Citi Parks, 1982-1991
  - City Theatre, 1979-2008
  - Civic Arena, 1962-2007
  - Clarion State College, 1976-1984
  - Clark Building Screening Room, 1989
  - Clark, Lynn, 1986
  - Clarke, Caitlin, 1981-2004
  - Close Company, 1983
  - Clowns, 1976-1984
  - Club 22
  - Cohen, Harold V., 1942
  - Coleman, Marilyn, 1987
  - Coleman, Stephen, 1991-2006
  - Coll, Jason, 1989-1990
  - College Club of Pittsburgh, 1915-1922
  - Comedy Clubs, 1981-1985
  - Community College of Allegheny County (all campuses, current), 1995-1996
  - Community of Healing Artists and Musicians in Performances, 1989
  - Community Players, 1935
  - Community Theatre Players of Ben Avon, 1992
  - Como, Perry, 1974-1976
  - Company Cabaret, 1983
  - Comtra Players, 1995-1996
  - ConcerTheater, 1987
  - Connelly, Marc, 1962-1990
  - Conner, Lynne, 1985-2008
  - Costello, Maurice, 1927-1931
  - Costello-Barrymore, Dolores, 1925-1981
  - Costume Design, 1990
  - Cousin, Tome, 1989-2002
  - Cox, Etta, 1987
  - Coyle Theatre, Charleroi, 1906
  - Crafton Players, 1941-1942
  - Crawford, Nan - SEE Broadway Players Stock Co., Lyceum Theater
  - Crossroads Theater Company, 1982
  - Cue and Curtain Players - McKeesport, 1937-1938
  - Cue and Curtain Players - SEE Young Men's Christian Association
  - Cullen, Bill, 1990
  - Curran, Robert, 1990
  - Curtaineers, 1950-1953
  - Custer, Shirley, 1995-2009
- D
  - Dance Schools - SEE Barth School of Dance, Olympic Studio of Dancing
  - Dantry, Jay, 1984
  - David L. Lawrence Convention Center, 1980
  - Davidson, John, 1990
  - Davis, Harry, 1940
  - Davis Theatre
  - Dear Friends: Ensemble for 19th Century American Music, 1989-1992
  - Delpheni Repertory Company, 1984-1985
  - Demundi Productions, 1976
  - Department of Public Works, Bureau of Recreation, 1937
  - De Ribere, Lisa, 1990
  - Deutsches Theater, 1923
  - Dewhurst, Colleen, 1974-1989
  - Dicesare Engler Productions, Inc., 1978-1979
  - DiPaolo, Elvira, 1990-1991
  - Documentaries - Misc., 1959-1982
  - Dracomtra Players, 1931-1934
  - Drama Festival of Allegheny Centennial, 1940
  - Dramaturgs, 1984
  - Dream Makers, 1977
  - Duggan, Danny, 1923-1950
  - Duncan, Isadora, 1918-1919
  - Dunn, Colleen, 2003
  - Duquesne Garden, 1927
  - Duquesne Garden, 1937-1938
  - Durning, Charles, 1990
  - Duse, Eleanora, 1924-2010
  - Dutton, Charles, 2007
  - Dvorsky, George, 1985
  - Dwyer, Ethel, 1985
- E
  - East End Theatre, 1897-1928
  - East Liberty Arts Council, 1990
  - Eberson, John - SEE Perry Theater
  - Ecumenical Liturgical Dance and Choreography Workshop and Retreat, 1991
  - Edgar Allan Poe Theatre - SEE Gemini Theatre
  - Edgewood Community Players, 1941-1992
  - Edison Hotel, 1991
  - Edmonds, Mark, 1990
  - Effinger, Marta, 1991
  - El-Hakawati, 1981-1989
  - Elson, Howard, 1989
  - The Empire, 1911-1918
  - Encore - SEE Dantry, Jay
  - Encore II, 1978
  - Enright Theatre, 1928-1990
  - Ernie's Esquire, 1976-1978
  - Epworthian Players
  - Esquire Players - SEE Ernie's Esquire
  - Evans, Maryetta, 1999-2009
  - Experimental Theatre, 1933-1977
  - Exposition Park
  - Expositions - SEE Festivals, Celebrations, Pageants, etc.
- F
  - Fairs - SEE Festivals, Celebrations, Pageants, etc.
  - Famous People Players, 1987
  - Famous Rider, 1983-1986
  - Famous Rider Cultural Center (formerly Fine Line), 1982-1987
  - Favorini, Attilio, 1976
  - Fayette Heritage, Inc. - Great Meadows Amphitheatre
  - Federation of Non-Commercial Theatres, 1942-1943
  - Female Impersonators, 1987-1991
  - Festivals, celebrations, pageants, etc., 1884-1991
  - Fifty-fifth Marionette Company - SEE Puppets
  - Fine Line Cultural Center - SEE Famous Rider Cultural Center
  - First Night, 1998-2008
  - The First Stage: Performing Arts for Children, 1975-1984
  - First Step 1985
  - Fitzgerald, Geraldine, 1986-1989
  - Fitzgerald, Richard, 1990
  - Flaherty, Stephen, 1990
  - Flashdance, 1982
  - Flying Dragon Puppet Theatre - SEE Puppets
  - Flying Pig Theatre, 1990-1995
  - Flynn, Winnie, 1982-1994
  - Fornes, Maria Irene, 1982-1986
  - Fort Pitt Hotel, 1935
  - Foster, Jodie, 1989-1990
  - Fourth River Poetry Festival, 1986
  - Fountain Room Restaurant
  - Fox Chapel Community Players, 1975-1982
  - Fox Chapel Playhouse, 1940
  - France, Richard, 1982
  - Franklin, Don, 1990
  - Fraternal Organizations, misc., 1929-1981
  - Frezza, Christine, 1987
  - Friday Night Club, 1886
  - Full House Ensemble, 1975
  - Fulton Theatre, 1983-1988
  - The Funny Bone - SEE Comedy Clubs
  - Future Tenant, 2005-current
- G
  - Gaelic Arts Society of Pittsburgh
  - Gagliano, Frank, 1985-1989
  - Garden Theatre, 1935-2007
  - Gardner, Bill, 1989-1990
  - Gateway Clipper Fleet - SEE Brockett, Don
  - Gateway Theatre - SEE Harris Theatres
  - Gateway to Music: Program for Schools, 1990-1991
  - Gay and Lesbian Film Festival, 1989-1995
  - Gay and Lesbian theatre - SEE ALSO Pittsburgh Queer Theatre, 1980-2003
  - Gayety Theatre, 1972-1981
  - Gemini Theater Co., 1996-1999
  - GenderBridge Theatre, 1992-1993
  - Generalovich, Tracy, 2003
  - Geneva College, 1975-2009
  - George, Kathleen, 1987-2006
  - George Sharp Players, 1972
  - Geruschat, Carl
  - Gill, Robert Stanton, 1943
  - Gillis, Susan, 1989
  - Gina's Restaurant, 1975
  - Giron, Arthur, 1989-1990
  - Glenshaw Players, 1955-1987
  - Goldblum, Jeff, 1977-1989
  - Golden Crucible - SEE Pittsburgh Bicentennial 1959
  - Goldmann, Bernhard, 1986
  - Gomez-Pena, Guillermo, 1994-1995
  - Gordon, Jeff, 1987-1990
  - Gorman Lowe Productions - SEE la Place
  - Gorshin, Frank, 1977-2005
  - Graffitti's Back Room
  - Graham, Martha, 1978-1981
  - Grand Opera House - SEE Warner Center, 1984
  - Grand - SEE Davis, Harry, 1897-1918
  - Grant, Lee, 1989-1991
  - Gray, Spalding, 1979-1992
  - The Great American Fourth of July parade - SEE United States Bicentennial 1976 (in Pennsylvania)
  - Great Meadows Amphitheatre - SEE ALSO Fayette Heritage, Inc., 1979-1980
  - Greater Connellsville Community Chorus
  - Greensburg Civic Theatre, 1976-current
  - GREX, 1993-1994
  - Greystone Productions, Inc., 1993
  - Grid, Ink. - SEE Performance Art, 1991-1994
  - Grise, Virginia, 2017
  - Grodin, Charles, 1974-1990
  - Gros, Jean - SEE Caravan School of Theatre Arts, 1937-1938
  - Grotto Cast Players, 1934
  - Grove City College, 1974-1984
- H
  - Hackney, Doris, 1951-1968
  - Hall, Kevin Peter, 1986-1991
  - Hamlet productions in Pittsburgh, 2003
  - Harmonie Associates, 1958-1961
  - Harper, Walt - SEE Walter Harper's Attic, Harper's
  - Harper's, 1986-1989
  - Harrigan, Peter, 1987-1991
  - Harris Amusement Co. - SEE Harris Theatres
  - Harris, John H. and John P. - SEE ALSO Harris Theatres, 1927-2005
  - Harris, Julie, 1989-1990
  - Harris' Musee Theatre - SEE ALSO Harris Theatres, 1901
  - Harris, Niki, 1987
  - Harris Senator Theatre - SEE ALSO Harris Theatres, 1941
  - Harris Theater - SEE ALSO Art Cinema, 2004-2007
  - Harris Theatres, 1924-2008
    SEE ALSO: Alvin Theatre, Davis, Harry, Gateway Theatre, Harris Amusement Co., Harris, John H. and John P., Harris Musee, Harris Senator, J.P. Harris Theatre, Theatres-History
  - Harrison, John, 1990
  - Harrold, Clarissa
  - Hartman, Elizabeth, 1987
  - Hartwood Acres, 1986-1989
  - Hazlett Theatre - SEE ALSO Allegheny Community Theatre, 1980-2004
  - Hazo, Sam - SEE ALSO Fulton Theatre, 1993
  - Hebron Theatre, 1991
  - Heinz Field
  - Heinz House, 1918-1928
  - Hensel, Christopher, 1991
  - Herman, Danny, 1990
  - Hillsdale Players, 1980
  - Hillside Players
  - Hiram College, 1952
  - Hissrich, Michael, 2003
  - Hodgetts, Eileen Enwright, 1993
  - Holbrook, Hal, 1962-1965
  - Holiday House, 1977-1986
  - Holiday Inn - Butler, 1974
  - Holiday Inn - Irwin - SEE Twin Rose Productions, Theatre-on-the-Ridge, Dinner-Theatre-on-the-Ridge, 1976-1979
  - Holiday Inn - North Hills
  - Holiday Park Players
  - Hollingsworth, Harry - SEE Broadway Players Stock Co., Lyceum Theater
  - Hollow Tree Players of Ligonier
  - Holt, John, 1993
  - Homewood-Brushton Renaissance Players, 1981-1982
  - Hoover, Ted, 1985-1991
  - Hopkins, Anthony, 1989-1990
  - Horne, Lena, 1968--current
  - Hospitals - The Pittsburgh Academy of Medicine, 1932-1984
  - Hotel Schenley, 1909-1934
  - Houdini, Harry, 1925-2009
  - Howe, Carolyn, 1989
- I
  - Ibsen productions in Pittsburgh, 1980
  - Ice shows, 1964-1994
  - Imaginarium, 1981
  - Improvisation Theater, 1990
  - In the Act Theater Co., 1990
  - Indiana Players, 1979-1982
  - Intergenerational Theatre Company, 1994
  - International Repertory Company, 1953-1972
  - International Theatre Pittsburgh - SEE International Repertory Co.
  - Invisible Village Theater Co.
  - Irene Kaufmann Settlement, 1920-1950
  - Irish Players, 1994
  - Irish Repertory Theatre Co., 1992
  - Irish Universities Theatre Co, 1987-1988
  - Iron City Ensembles, 1977
  - Iron City Mime Troupe, 1976
  - Iron City Theatre, 1984-1985
  - Irwin Little Theatre, 1941
  - Islam Grotto - SEE Cast Players
  - ISO, 1989
- J
  - J.P. Harris Theatre - SEE ALSO Harris Theatres, 1942
  - Jackson, Anne, 1976-1979
  - James Street Theatre, 1988
  - Jay-Lou Productions
  - Jean Carr Theatrical Agency, 1982
  - Jewish Community Center of Pittsburgh - SEE Center Stage Players, Experimental Theatre, Young Men and Women's Hebrew Association, 2001
  - Jewish Theatre of Pittsburgh, 2001-2006
  - John Holt Productions
  - Johnson, Bob, 1982-1984
  - Jolson, Al, 1914-1972
  - Jones, Shirley, 1945-current
  - Jovavich, Scott, 1986-1989
  - Joyner, Mario, 1986
  - Junior League
- K
  - Kaiden, Elizabeth, 2003
  - Kamin, Dan, 1979-1991
  - Kanders, Helene, 1918-1919
  - Kane, Carol - SEE "When a Stranger Calls"
  - Kane, Janet, 1978
  - Katselas, Milton, 1975-2008
  - Katz, Leon - SEE Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre, 1977-1983
  - Kaufman, George S., 1918-current
  - Kaufman, George Sothern, 1902
  - Kaufmann's Children's Center, 1937
  - Kaup, Paul, 1989-1990
  - Kean Theatre, 2006-2012
  - Keaton, Buster, 1905-1907
  - Keaton, Michael - SEE Pittsburgh Poor Players Inc., 1988-1990
  - Kelly, Frederick N., 1938-2004
  - Kelly, Gene, 1941-current
  - Kenley Players, 1975-1984
  - Kennedy, Dennis, 1988-1990
  - Kennilworth
  - Kenyon, Elmer
  - Kilbuck Players
  - Kilbuck Theatre, 1936-1939
  - Kinetic Theatre Company, 2014-current
  - Kings Court Theater, 1990
  - Kingdom, Bob, 1990
  - Kiralfy Brothers
  - Kirk, Lisa, 1972-1984
  - Klinger, Cindi and Pam, 1984
  - Knaiz, Judy, 1963-1969
  - Knickerty Knockerty Children's Theatre, 1954-1957
  - Komperda, Edward L., 1990
  - Kording Kraft Players - SEE Silver Fox Playhosue
  - Kramer's Back Room, 1968
  - Krenn, Otto, 1946-1993
  - Kurosawa Koto Ensemble, 1990
- L
  - Labor plays - Misc., 1980-1981
  - Laboratory Theatre, 1939-1964
  - Lacey, Florence, 1979-1990
  - Lamberts, Heath, 1974-2005
    Acquisition Information
    The majority of the contents of this folder were donated by Louise Silk in 2005.
  - Lamhut, Phyllis
  - Langley High School, 1978
  - Langevin, Kenneth, 1990
  - Lapiduss, Maxine and Sally, 1981-1984
  - LaPore, Janyce, 1988
  - La Roche College, 1984-2009
  - Latshaw Productions, 1992-1993
  - Lawrence Loft, 1986
  - Leech, Bill, 1989
  - Lemming Project, 1985
  - Leona Theatre, 1982-1983
  - Lerner, Mimi, 1978-1991
  - Leslie, Diane, 1980
  - Lester Hamburg Studio Theater
  - Letchworth, Eileen, 1966-1967
  - Levant, Oscar, 1972
  - Liberty Theatre, 1913-1983
  - Ligonier Valley Players, 1979
  - Linn, David, 1936-1945
  - Lion Walk - SEE ALSO Pennsylvania Repertory Theatre, Fine Line Cultural Center, 1978-1980
  - Little Theatre of Tarentum, 1940-1941
  - Living Theatre, 1968-1975
  - Lloyd Lauren, 1990
  - Lloyd, Patricia, 1981
  - Lockerman, Bradley, 1986
  - Loomer, Lisa, 1990
  - Lovelace, Margo, 2022
  - Ludlam, Charles, 1974-1990
  - Lyceum Theater - SEE ALSO Broadway Players Stock Co., 1911-1998
  - Lynn, Marcy, 1989
  - Lyric Opera Company, 1975
  - Lyric Theatre, Inc., 1953-1955
- M
  - MCT Valley Playhouse - SEE Monroeville Civic Theatre
  - M&M Productions, 1976
  - Maazel, Lorin, 1986-1990
  - MacFarlane, James W., 1936
  - Mairs, David, 1990
  - Maguire, George, 1980
  - Magic and magicians, 1976-1986
  - Maloney, Kevin, 1990
  - Manchester Craftsmen's Guild, 1988-1990
  - Mancini, Henry, 1987-1990
  - Manestage, 1980
  - Marionette Theatre Arts Council - SEE Puppets
  - Marionettes - SEE Puppets
  - Marke, Sid, 1977
  - Market Square Inn, 1979
  - Market Square Playhouse, 1975
  - Market Square Theatre, 1987-1989
  - Marriott - Green Tree, 1983-1985
  - Marshall, Donald, 1988
  - Marshall, Kathleen, 2006-2017
  - Marshall, Robby, 1980-2003
  - Martin, Melissa, 1987
  - Masquers, The, 1936-1937
  - Mathis, Lee, 1982
  - Mattress Factory, 1978-1992
  - Maurer, Kelly, 1985
  - May Beegle Concerts - SEE Syria Mosque
  - McClintock, Jodie Lynne, 1983-1986
  - McCrady, Ethel Dwyer - SEE Dwyer, Ethel
  - McCurdy Arts Complex, 1985
  - McElroy, Michael, 1989-1991
  - McGovern, Michael, 1989
  - McKee Place Productions, McKee Place School - SEE Schools--Misc., 1980--, 1980-1985
  - McKeesport Little Theater, 1987-1996
  - McKeown, Pat, 1989-1990
  - McMillan, Richard - SEE T.R.S.F. 1988/89, Playhouse 1989, Twelfth Night, Shaw Fest 1991, 1981-1990
  - Mellon Bank Club Players, 1940
  - Mellwood Playhouse
  - Melodia, 1979-1986
  - Melody Amphitheatre, 1989-1990
  - Mendler, Skip, 1988-1989
  - Menjou, Adolph, 1979
  - Menken, Adah Issacs, 1968
  - Mennino, Mary-Therese, 1990-1991
  - Merchant, John, 1990
  - Merrie Operetta Co., 1969-1974
  - Mertz, Doug, 2002
  - Meyran Theater, 1914-1915
  - Miller, Burton, 1977-1983
  - Miller, Dennis - SEE ALSO Comedy Clubs, Portfolio, 1986-1991
  - Miller, Madge, 1976-1984
  - Miller, Mary, 1989-1990
  - Milnes, Sherril, 1990
  - Minniefield, David, 1994